

CONTACT ME AT

Phone : 087783877452

Email : dian.agustina206@gmail.com

Linked in : dian agustina

Github : https://dianagustina19.github.io/

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Html5
- PHP
- MySQL
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Css
- Bootstrap
- SQL Server
- Oracle
- Laravel Framework

LANGUAGE

- <u>B</u>ahasa
- English

DIAN AGUSTINA

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Graduated with a bachelor's degree in information system from Gunadarma University. I am a person who has passion and good discipline that is always applied.

Good at analyst, planning and communication, I am very passionate in doing website development, and i have experience creating website.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

PT Tripasysfo Development | October 2019 - May 2020

 Build the whole backend for reporting website using Laravel framework

Software Engineer Front End

PT Rupi Digital Indonesia | August 2020 - May 2021

- Build Web Monitoring Using Laravel Framework
- Build Web Reporting Using Laravel Framework
- Build Web Integrated API
- Add Features to Existing Websites
- Using Scrum Method

PERSONAL PROJECT

1. Freelance

Client: PT. Karya Utama Gama (KUGAMA)
Make some modules using laravel framework.

- Client: PT. Musik Hanamidori

Develop Company Profile Using PHP and Mysql

EDUCATION

Gunadarma University

Information System | 2015 - 2019

Last GPA: 3.43